Guide to the Lynne Tillman Papers 1939-2008 (Bulk 1984-2006) MSS 180 MSS 180
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Series I, Subseries A: Individuals and Institutions
    - Neilson, Melanie, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Nemet-Nejat, Murat, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Neri, Louise, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - nest: A Quarterly Magazine of Interiors, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Neurath, Thomas, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - New Directions: Publishing Corporation, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - New Langdon Arts, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - New Literary History, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - The New Museum of Contemporary Art, 1985-1998 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - New Observations, 1984-1997 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - New York Foundation for the Arts, 1991-1999 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - New York Institute for the Humanities at NYU, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - The New York Public Library, Undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - The New York State Council on the Arts / Gregory Kolovakos / Jewelle L. Gomez, 1988-1993 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - The New York Times, 1989-2000 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - New York University, 1999-2004 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - NYU Medical Center, 2000-2002 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - NYU Press, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - The New Yorker, 1983-2001 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Newman, John, Undated (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Newsday, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Newton, David, 1996-2002 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Nicholson, Annable, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Nicolazzini, Piergiorgio, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Niedzviecki, Hal, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - NIGHT, 1991-1995 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Niimoto, Riyo, Undated (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Noble, Aaron, c.a. 1984 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Norton, Margot, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Novakov, Anna, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Nufer, Doug, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Nutting, Cherie, 1995-2002 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - O'Toole, Laurence, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Obst, Deiter, 1984-1989 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Odell, David, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - The Ohio State University, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Oisteanu, Valery and Ruth, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Oklahoma State University, Undated (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - One Meadway, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Oppenheim, Lisa, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Oppenheim, Meret, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Oregon Art Institute, Northwest Film & Video Center, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Orr, Carol Wallace, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Otcu, Onder, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Otis School of Art and Design, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Owens, Jim and Bette, 1993-2000 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Özkaya, Serkan, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Pace University, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Pantheon Books, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - PARKETT: Art Magazine / Kunstzeitschrift, 1992-1995 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Passagen Verlag, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Pavillion Books, 1994-1999 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Pauter, Nicole, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Pearl, Monica, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - PEN American Center, 1998-2005 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Penguin, 1990-2002 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Penny, Bridget, 1993-1999 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Pera, Brian, Undated (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Perlman, Cara, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Petropoulos, Renee, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Phaidon Press Limited, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Phillips, Caryl (Caz), 1991-1999 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - Phillips, Christopher, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - Piper, Adrian, Undated (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Plantenga, Bart, c.a. 1991 (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - Plate, Peter, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Ploof, John, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Ploughshares / Paul Muldoon, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - The Poetry Project, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Points de Fuite, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Pollock, Jim, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Pollock-Krasner Foundation, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Poorbaugh, Cindy, 1995-1997 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Porter, Joe Ashby, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Poseidon Press, 1987-1993 (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Preiss, Jeff, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Preserved Fish Productions, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - Prina, Stephen, 1986-1995 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Prince, Richard, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Prior, Amy, 1997-2002 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Proctor, Minna, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Public Art Fund, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Pullinger, Kate, 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Purdy, James, Undated (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Purdy, Janet, Undated (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Pushcart Press, 1985-2004 (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Quackenbush, Jan, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Rabinowitz, Jon, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Raff, Orit, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Raftery, Karen, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Rain Taxi: Review of Books, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Rainer, Yvonne, 1991-2000 (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Rampike, Undated (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Randall, Margaret, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 136)
    - Random House, 1985-2004 (Box 5, Folder 137)
    - Rankin, Aimee, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 138)
    - Rattray, David, 1977-1985 (Box 5, Folder 139)
    - Reaktion Books Ltd, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 140)
    - Recorded Books, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 141)
    - Red Bass, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 142)
    - Redstone Press, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 143)
    - Reed, Judith, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 144)
    - Regan, Marie, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 145)
    - Reiner, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 146)
    - La République Internationale des Lettres / Noël Blandin, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 147)
    - Rertzelos, Pauline, Undated (Box 5, Folder 148)
    - Rettallade, Joan, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 149)
    - Review of Contemporary Fiction, Undated (Box 5, Folder 150)
    - Rexroth, Stevie, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 151)
    - Rhett, Kathryn, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 152)
    - Ribot, Marc, 1993-1996 (Box 5, Folder 153)
    - Rice, Doug, Undated (Box 5, Folder 154)
    - Ridgefield Press, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 155)
    - Riley, (Elizabeth) Denise, 1991-2002 (Box 5, Folder 156)
    - Robbins, Jack, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 157)
    - The Robert Lantz - Joy Harris Literary Agency, Inc., 1990-1996 (Box 5, Folder 158)
    - Rochon, Sidonie, 1975-2001 (Box 5, Folder 159)
    - Rochou, Aidocie, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 160)
    - Roeseler, Karl, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 161)
    - Rohn, Bob, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 162)
    - Root, Jane / The Media Show, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 163)
    - Rose, Joel and Catherine Texier / Love on the Edge, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Rosenberg, Alan, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Rosenberg, Aura, 1995-1998 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Ross, Andrew, 1997-2001 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Ross, Melanie, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Ross-Erikson, Inc., Publishers, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Rothenberger, Manfred, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Rowe, Marsha, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Rower, Ann, Undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - The Russian Samovar / James [Wilson], 2003 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - S. Fischer Verlag, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Sabin, Stefana, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Saint Mark's Bookshop, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - St. Martin's Press, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Salerno, Linda, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - San Francisco Art Institute, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Sanford J. Greenburger Associates Inc., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Sarah Lazin Books, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Saul, Paul, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Scalapino, Leslie, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Scalo (re: Roni Horn), 1997 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Schambelan, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Schlupmann, Heide, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Schmeiser, Jo, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Schoffelen, Jos, 1971-2003 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Scholder, Amy ***see also*** High Risk ***see also*** Serpent's Tail, 1988-1998 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - School of Visual Arts, Photography Department, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Schouten, Lydia, 1992-1998 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Scott, James and Yolanda Orozco, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Scott, Susan, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Screen Actors Guild - Producers Pension And Health Plans, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Scribner / Simon & Schuster, Inc., 2001 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Scrivner, Jay ***see also*** Stadler, Matthew, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Searle, Adrian, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - the Seattle Review, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Second Shift, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Segrave, Elisa, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Seigle, Iris, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Seigle, Jane, 1987-1997 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Seigle, Robert, 1987-1997 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Seip, Mattijn, c.a. 2000 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Seltzer, Hara, 1995-1999 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Semiotext(e), 2001 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Sengupta, Somini and Hans van de Weerd, 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Seriously Inc./Management for Living Colour, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Serpent's Tail, 1988-2003 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Seven Stories, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Shakespeare & Co. Bookstore, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Shapiro-Maren, Dani, Michael and Jacob, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Sharpe, Matt, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Shaver, Nancy, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Shaviro, Steve, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Sheck, Laurie, Undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Sheffield, Elizabeth and Jeffrey, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Sherman, Cindy, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Shimo, Seiichiro, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Shohl, David, 1996-1999 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Shore, Stephen/Staphan and Ginger, c.a. 2005 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Sickels, Amy, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Sikorski, Rob, Undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Sillman, Amy, 1977-2002 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Silverberg, Ira ***see also*** High Risk *** see also*** Serpent's Tail, 1992-2004 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Simmons, Laurie, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Simon & Schuster, Undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Small Press Traffic, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Smith, Donny, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Smith, Kiki, 1984-1999 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Smith, Seton, c.a. 2000 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Smithsonian Institution, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Snedman, Lorna, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - S.I.T.T. (Societe Internationale Transit Transport), c.a. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Society For The Right To Die, c.a. 1991 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Soft Skull Press, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Sohn, Miyoung, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Sonberg, Warren, 1970-1993 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Song, Suran, 1996-2001 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Sorrentino, Christopher, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - The South Bank Centre, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - South Street Seaport Museum, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Spahr, Juliana, Undated (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Sphinx, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Springfield, Susan, 1981-1998 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Spuyten Duyvil, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Stadler, Matthew, 1992-2002 (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Stallings, Tyler, 1991-1995 (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Stanford University Libraries, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - SUNY Buffalo, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1995-2005 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Steiner, Eurydice, 1996-2001 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - Steinke, Darcey, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - Sterling-Pierce Co., Inc., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - Stern, Lesley, 1982-1997 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Stockholder, Jessica, 1995-2000 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - Stone, Andrew, Undated (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - Stone, Susan, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Stop Over Press, 1994-1996 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Stop the War, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - Storrie, Calum, [1994] (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Stroemfeld/Roter Stern, 1985-1998 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - SUN, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - Sung, Stella C. Y., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Surface Tension: Lesbian, Straight and Bisexual Women Write About Their Friendships / Meg Daly, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Sweitzer, Jody / TAB, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Swift, Graham, 1993-2000 (Box 6, Folder 95)
    - Synchronization, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 96)
    - Tabbi, Joseph, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Tamang, Indra, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 98)
    - Tantimedh, Adisakdi, 1990-1991 (Box 6, Folder 99)
    - Tax, Sissi, c.a. 2002 (Box 6, Folder 100)
    - Tessa, David, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 101)
    - Tewes, Robin, 1997-1999 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Third Wave Foundation, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Thorne, Ann, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Tickner, Lisa, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Time Out, 1996-2000 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Tin House Magazine, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Tinling, David C., 1991 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Tinney, Christopher, c.a. 2000 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Tobier, Nick, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Toiben, Colm, 1992-1997 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Topolski, Teresa, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Topp, Mike, 199- (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Torberg, Peter, 1995-1998 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Toshiba, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Treadwell, Elizabeth, 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Trinidad, David, 1983-2003 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Trip Street Press, 1995-2001 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Trippi, Laura, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Tronnier, Claudia, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Trophy Nut Co., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Truitt, Sam, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Tsyskus, Gork, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Turtle Point Press / Jonathan D. Rabinowitz, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Turyn, Anne, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Tuttle-Mori Agency, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Tyer, Brad, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Tyler Galleries, Tyler School of Art, Temple University, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Ulin, David L., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Ultimatum, Undated (Box 6, Folder 130)
    - UPS, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 131)
    - United University Professions, Undated (Box 6, Folder 132)
    - University Art Museum, SUNY Albany, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 133)
    - University of Maryland, Baltimore County, Center for Art and Visual Culture, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 134)
    - University of Pennsylvania, The School of Veterinary Medicine, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 135)
    - The University of Tennessee Press, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 136)
    - Unmuzzled Ox: Books & Magazine, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 137)
    - Urchueguia, Cristina and KD Wolff, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 138)
    - Valentine, Jean, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 139)
    - Van den Bosch, Annette, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 140)
    - Vaughn, Allan, c.a. 1965 (Box 6, Folder 141)
    - Venero, Isabel, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 142)
    - Venezky, Elie, c.a. 1994 (Box 6, Folder 143)
    - The Venus Girls, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 144)
    - verlagsauslieferungen, 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 145)
    - Vermont College of Norwich University, MFA in Visual Art, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 146)
    - Veronese, David, Undated (Box 6, Folder 147)
    - Viegener, Matias, 1990-1995 (Box 6, Folder 148)
    - Viking / Penguin Books Ltd, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 149)
    - The Village Voice, 1991-1999 (Box 6, Folder 150)
    - Vintage / Random House UK Ltd., 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - Virginia Center for the Creative Arts, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Vogue, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Volkman, K, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - von Schlegell, Mark, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - W. W. Norton & Company, 1990-2001 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Wachovia Securities, Inc., 2002 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Wanzer, Lizette E., 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Ware, Vron, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Wargolwala, Andrew, 1989-1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Warsh, Lewis, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Watney, Simon, 1989-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Watson, Carl, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Watson, Don, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Watson (Sanger), Jeannette, 1997-2004 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Watson, Steven, 1998-[2001] (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Waxman, Lynn and Ron, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Weigel, Tom, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Weinstein, Elissa, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Weinstock, Jane, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Weissman, Benjamin, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Welling, Jim, 1995-[2000] (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Wessells, Henry, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Westbeth Artists, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Westmoreland, Joe, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Wexner Center, 1993-2001 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Wheeler, Susan, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - White, Ed, 1993-2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - White, Garrett, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Whitewalls: A Journal of Language and Art, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1993-1999 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Wiener, Alan, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Wilentz, Joan and Ted, 1998-2000 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Wilkinson, Wendell, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Willbern, David, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Williams, Heathcote, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Williams, Tyrone, 1993-1997 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Wilson, Martha ***see also*** Franklin Furnace, 1983-2001 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Wittig, R. A., 1991 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - WNYC, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - WNYU, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Wollen, Peter, 1985-1991 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Women's Audio Archive, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - The Wood family, 1992-2000 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - WoodBrown, V. Diane, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Woronov, Mary, c.a. 2000 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Wortsman, Peter, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Wray, John, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Wright, C. D., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - The Wrong Gallery / Lori, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - XanEdu Publishing Services, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Yablonsky, Linda, 1995-2002 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Yapar, Cengiz, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - York, Nora, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Yormy, James, Undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Young, Elizabeth Jesse, 1991-2001 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Yourgrau, Barry, c.a. 1993 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Yuknavitch, Lidia, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Zabelskis, Peter, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Zahler, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Zivancevic, Nina, 1985-1998 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Zone Books, Undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Zubillaga, Fernando and Isadora, 2001-2003 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Zuibovich, Vredy and Tom, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Series I, Subseries B: Incomplete Names / Illegible / Unsigned / Other Correspondence
    Note that there may be multiple addressers under the same first name or initial. For example, the folder titled "John" contains correspondence from more than one sender, all signed "John."
    - Abigail, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Adam, 1973, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Adi, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Al, Undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Aleni, Undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Ali, Undated (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Alison, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Alta, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Ameena, Undated (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Amichel, Undated (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Amy and Tanner, c.a. 2000 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Andronovich, Undated (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Andy, c.a. 1977 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Ann, c.a. 1997 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Anthony, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Ariel, Undated (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Asher, Ira and Rebecca *, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Aurelia, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - B., 1978-1995 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Barbara, 1974-1993 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Bertie, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Betsy, Undated (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Bill, 1975-1992 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Bill H., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Bill and Patty, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Bob, 1975-1992 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Brad, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Brian, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - C., 1975-1994 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - C. P., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Carla, Undated (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Carole, 1995-2000 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Carolee, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Carolyn, Christopher, Vivian, 2006 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Charles, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Charles R., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Charlie, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Cheryl, Undated (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Chris, c.a. 1979 (Box 7, Folder 102)
    - Christine, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Christopher / Program in Writing and Humanistic Studies, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Chuck, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Cilia S., 1994-2003 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Claude, c.a. 1993 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Connie, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 108)
    - Constance, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 109)
    - Craig, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 110)
    - Crosley, Undated (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - Cynthia, Undated (Box 7, Folder 112)
    - D., c.a. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Dale, c.a. 1994 (Box 7, Folder 114)
    - Dan, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Dana, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Daniel, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Darcey, Undated (Box 7, Folder 118)
    - Daryl, 1977-1985 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - David, 1973-2000 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - David and Clay, Undated (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Dawn, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 122)
    - Deb / Victoria College, Undated (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Dennes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Dennis, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 125)
    - Dian[a]/[e], 1975-1999 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Didie, c.a. 1995 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Diego *, Undated (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Dierdre, c.a. 1989 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Donna, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Doug, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Douglas, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - E., 2000 (Box 7, Folder 133)
    - Ed, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Edith, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Eileen, 1983-2000 (Box 7, Folder 136)
    - Elinor, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 137)
    - Eliza, 1990-2003 (Box 7, Folder 138)
    - Eve, c.a. 2003 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Faith / Bittersweet Farm, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 140)
    - Francois, c.a. 1992 (Box 7, Folder 141)
    - Frank, Undated (Box 7, Folder 142)
    - Frantizka, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 143)
    - Fred, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Fiona, 1983-1998 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - G., Undated (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - [Ganti], 1991 (Box 7, Folder 147)
    - Gary, 1984-1995 (Box 7, Folder 148)
    - Geo, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 149)
    - George, 19[--]-2000 (Box 7, Folder 150)
    - Geraldine, Undated (Box 7, Folder 151)
    - Gerard, 1972-1979 (Box 7, Folder 152)
    - Gillian, Undated (Box 7, Folder 153)
    - Glenda, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 154)
    - Gloria, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 155)
    - Grace, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 156)
    - Gregg, 1993-2000 (Box 7, Folder 157)
    - Gregory, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 158)
    - H., c.a. 1993 (Box 7, Folder 159)
    - Hajime, Undated (Box 7, Folder 160)
    - hero, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 161)
    - Hilary and Phillip and Moss, Undated (Box 7, Folder 162)
    - Ida, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 163)
    - [Cohen, Ira], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 164)
    - Inge and Bill, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 165)
    - Ismeil and Jan, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - Iwona B., Undated (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - J., Undated (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - James, 1992-1994 (Box 7, Folder 169)
    - James B., 1984 (Box 7, Folder 170)
    - Jan, Undated (Box 7, Folder 171)
    - Jane, 1983-1997 (Box 7, Folder 172)
    - Janet, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 173)
    - [Janett], 1995 (Box 7, Folder 174)
    - Janice, 1974-1992 (Box 7, Folder 175)
    - Jason and Derek, c.a. 2000 (Box 7, Folder 176)
    - Javier, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 177)
    - Jean, 1979-1995 (Box 7, Folder 178)
    - Jeff, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 179)
    - Jeffrey and Lisa, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 180)